

CONTACT

CARLOS ARMANDO LOPEZ ESPINOZA

(686) 228 68 11

CALOPEZ9616@GMAIL.COM

MEXICALI, BAJA CALIFORNIA, MÉXICO

SKILLS

HTML + CSS + BOOTSTRAP

JAVASCRIPT

C# + ASP .NET 6

PHP + LARAVEL

JAVA + SPRINGBOOT

FLUTTER + DART

SQL

LANGUAGE

ENGLISH

SOCIAL





CARLOS LÓPEZ WEB DEVELOPER











ABOUT ME

WEB DEVELOPER WITH 4 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE IN APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT, 2 YEARS WAS A PROFESSIONAL WAY DOING TECHNOLOGICAL SOLUTIONS FROM REQUIREMENTS OF EACH COMPANY THAT I WORKED AND APPLYING THE BEST PRACTICES OF SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT WITH ARCHITECTURES THAT LET ME MAKE A SCALABLE SYSTEM.

EDUCATION

2016-2019

LICENCIADO EN SISTEMAS COMPUTACIONALES UNIVERSIDAD AUTONÓMA DE BAJA CALIFORNIA UNIVERSITY, MEXICALI, B.C.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BRANIX

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

MARCH 2020 - NOW

- ONE OF PRINCIPAL DEVELOPERS OF THE MEXLOG 3.0 PROJECT DEVELOPED FOR MEXICANA LOGISTICS COMPANY, WHICH ALLOW MANAGEMENT IN THE DIFFERENT AREAS SUCH AS INVENTORY, UNITS TRANSPORT, EMPLOYEES, ETC.
- DEVELOPMENT OF BILLING API 3.3 AND 4.0 IN MEXICO ALLOWING THE INTEGRATION IN DIFFERENTS PROJECTS FROM A NUGET PACKAGE OR DLL.
- A NUGETPACKAGE SERVER CONFIGURATION.
- ONE OF PRINCIPAL DEVELOPERS OF THE BNXLOGISTICS PROJECT, WHICH ALLOW THE MANAGEMENT OF COMMODITY TRANSPORTATION, INVENTORY, EMPLOYEES, ETC.

FREELANCER

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER.

OCTOBER 2018 - NOW

- WEB PAGE DESIGN FOR HIELO ESTRELLA COMPANY
- DEVELOPMENT OF A WEB SYSTEM FOR HIELO ESTRELLA COMPANY TO SALES CONTROL, INVENTORY, EMPLOYEES MANAGEMENT, ETC.
- DEVELOPMENT OF A WEB SYSTEM FOR DIGITALIZED PDF CONTROL AND GENERATION OF ELECTRONIC SIGNATURE FOR UABC.
- DEVELOPMENT OF A WEB SYSTEM FOR MANAGEMENT OF INVENTORY, EMPLOYEES AND OPERATION MANAGEMENT FOR THE IQS SERVICES COMPANY.
- SUPERVISION OF WEB PAGE DESIGN FOR HELADOS RICCO COMPANY.

MORE HABILITIES

- MICROSOFT OFFICE
- ADOBE PHOTOSHOP
- INTERNET INFORMATION SERVICES(IIS)
- ELECTRONIC BILLING(SAT 4.0 AND QUICKBOOKS)
- VISUAL STUDIO 2019
- VISUAL STUDIO CODE
- SQL MANAGEMENT STUDIO

